<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lambda-class</title>
    <link>http://lambda-class.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lambda-class</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 12:41:13 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://lambda-class.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Custom Renderers</title>
      <link>http://lambda-class.com/post/customrender/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 12:41:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lambda-class.com/post/customrender/</guid>
      <description>What is a Custom Renderer A Custom Renderer is a developer made Renderer Class that customises the appearance and behaviour of a UI control. The Renderer Class is responsible for creating the Xamarin.Forms representation of pages, layouts or controls for each platform (IOS, Android or Windows Phone). An alternative to Custom Renderers is the development of Custom Controls through subclassing.
The Custom Renderer Class is a derived class implementation of the Renderer Class responsible for rendering the corresponding UI object in each platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node.js Optimization</title>
      <link>http://lambda-class.com/post/flamegraph/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 09:46:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lambda-class.com/post/flamegraph/</guid>
      <description>0x a Node.js Optimization Tool I will show a tool called 0x that generates a Flame Graph. My goal is to give an overview of the tool. You can access a full step by step tutorial and learn how to use it by accessing the full article in TUNING NODE.JS APP PERFORMANCE WITH AUTOCANNON AND 0X by Ron Litzenberger. This tool was presented at the Node Interactive North America 2017 Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Grid Layout Module</title>
      <link>http://lambda-class.com/post/css-grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 16:44:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lambda-class.com/post/css-grid/</guid>
      <description>About the new CSS Grid Layout Module aka CSS Grid CSS Grid is a new method of using a grid concept to lay out content in an HTML page. It provides a mechanism for developers to divide available space for layout into columns and rows using a set of predictable sizing behaviours. CSS Grid will not only make it easy for developers to layout the most complicated designs but also, will make it possible to create designs that could not be implemented through other available solutions, such as Flexbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Project</title>
      <link>http://lambda-class.com/post/xamarin-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 15:01:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lambda-class.com/post/xamarin-project/</guid>
      <description>Using Xamarin Forms as an App Development Platform A brief description of the platform and the project I am working with some of the pros and cons I faced when starting to develop using Xamarin. What is Xamarin and How it works Xamarin is a development platform to build native apps for multiple platforms on a shared C# codebase. It uses the same IDE, language, and APIs to code apps for Android, IOS and Windows Phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://lambda-class.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:28:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lambda-class.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Alexandre Santigo da Silva E-mail: alex.santiago.mail@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://lambda-class.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 20:28:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lambda-class.com/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Alexandre, and I am from Brazil. I arrived in Canada in 2016 to study in the Web and Mobile Development and Design Program at Langara College.
I have over 12 years of experience in research and product development for the Health and Financial industries. Experienced in Java, c#, JavaScript, HTML and CSS, databases like MS SQL Server, MySQL and Oracle.
I also have experience in project management using PMI Organization standards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>